http://www.lamerie.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentHome/Privacy PolicyOur privacy policyEffective on May 14, 2018Our Commitment To PrivacyThis privacy statement describes how LA MERIE PUBLISHING collects and uses the personal information you provide on our websites: pipelinereview.com and lamerie.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.European Union General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)As required by Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of April 26, 2016, LA MERIE PUBLISHING follows the General Data Protection Regulation in order to protect your rights regarding personal information.Should you have any question regarding your personal data, please contact us (info@lamerie.com or +49 7934-6839 668)Personal Information GatheringWe collect the following personal information from you:When you browse our websiteTechnical Information such as your IP address, browser type and operating system, referring/exit pages, pages viewed, access datesWhen you ask for a product or service informationContact details such as email, last & first name, phone number, company nameWhen you create your accountContact details such as email, last & first nameWhen you purchase a product or serviceBilling Information such as credit card details (number, expiration, CVC) and billing addressCompany related Information such as company name, phone number, industry, size and revenues, VAT number, and your job title & positionPreferences Information such as browsing & order history, marketing preferencesStorage & Use of Personal InformationWe store and use your personal information to:Provide you with a user accountFulfill your ordersSend you order confirmationsAssess the needs of your business to determine suitable productsSend you requested product or service informationSend product updates or warranty informationSend you newslettersSend you marketing communications from LA MERIE PUBLISHINGAnswer to your questions and concernsImprove our platformComply with legal / tax obligations regarding applicable lawsPlease note we do not store your complete credit card informations in our own systems.Your rightsGeneral GuidanceAs per the GPDR, you have the rights to:Have your data rectified / updatedHave your data removed from our systemGet access to the personal data we stored about youIf you don’t have an account or for any other matter regarding your personal data and these rights, please contact us via the channels outlined at the bottom of the page.Communications Opt-OutYou may also choose to stop receiving our newsletters or marketing communications by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails at the bottom of the e-mail or you can contact us at info@lamerie.com .Information Obtained from Third PartiesIf you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.Information Sharings & TransfersGeneral GuidanceWe do not rent or sell your personal information to third parties.Transfers to third partiesWe also use third parties to ensure you the best service and may need to transfer parts of your information to these third parties, such as:An emailing platform. We may transfer your email, last & first name, company industry to send you marketing communications.Payment platforms (e.g. Concardis, Stripe). We transfer your credit card details to process your payment.We may also disclose your personal information:as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal processwhen we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,if LA MERIE PUBLISHING is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.PaypalIf you choose to use PayPal to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number directly to PayPal. PayPal’s privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal website.Cookies and Other Tracking TechnologiesLA MERIE PUBLISHING cookiesWe use cookies to ensure you the best quality of service, especially ease your navigation on our website. Cookies are used to store:your authentication token if you’re logged insome profile information & preferences when you’re not logged in, such as your country, currency, landing pagesThird parties tracking technologiesOur Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.We also use third parties cookies to gather information about how you and others use our website. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used. They do not include personal informationManaging cookies and trackingManaging your cookies preferencesYou can disable your cookies from your browser settings (see instructions below). Please note that disabling cookies might degrade your experience on our website and shall make it impossible to log in or purchase any product or service.Chrome: https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en&hlrm=enFirefox: https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferencesInternet Explorer: https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookiesEdge: https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacySafari: https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201265Other browsers: please read the manufacturer documentationManaging your tracking preferencesYou can disable anonymous third parties tracking directly from your browser settings (“do not track”).Chrome: https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/114836?Firefox: https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/how-do-i-turn-do-not-track-featureInternet Explorer: https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17288/windows-internet-explorer-11-use-do-not-trackEdge: https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacySafari: https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT206565Other browsers: please read the manufacturer documentationSecurityWhen we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact us at info@lamerie.comWe will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at info@lamerie.com . We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.Additional Policy InformationNotification of Privacy Statement ChangesWe may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.Links to Other websitesOur Site includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of LA MERIE PUBLISHING. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any website you visit.Contact InformationYou can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:La Merie Publishing – Ulrich MartinCarrer Garraf, 20, Bajos, 1a08870 SitgesSpainEmail: info@lamerie.com Phone: +49 7934-6839 668Fax: +49 3212 1267 572
